[{"answer": "No.", "docId": "130120pmt", "aSentId": 35, "question": "You know why I think they're so excited to see you?", "qSentId": 34}, {"answer": "I don't know but I --", "docId": "130120pmt", "aSentId": 48, "question": "Was it Daniel Craig or Denzel Washington who got Oscar nominated?", "qSentId": 47}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "130120pmt", "aSentId": 73, "question": "That wasn't too big a build-up there, Doug?", "qSentId": 72}, {"answer": "This is Barack Obama at his best.", "docId": "130120pmt", "aSentId": 78, "question": "When you watched him tonight, did you feel like I did, you saw a man more at peace with himself perhaps now ready for the challenge of maybe being some real action in the second term?", "qSentId": 77}, {"answer": "Well, my hope is it's going to be very significant.", "docId": "130120pmt", "aSentId": 85, "question": "How significant is that going to be in his second term?", "qSentId": 84}, {"answer": "I think it does.", "docId": "130120pmt", "aSentId": 92, "question": "Does that bring with it a certain stability to the administration of the United States?", "qSentId": 91}, {"answer": "You know, but think about second term Dwight Eisenhower.", "docId": "130120pmt", "aSentId": 112, "question": "Is that going to be a significant help to him?", "qSentId": 111}, {"answer": "Well, there's all this stuff that's been on the table, you know, that's been talked about in the media, immigration reform.", "docId": "130120pmt", "aSentId": 130, "question": "What should he be looking to do?", "qSentId": 129}, {"answer": "Well, I think ultimately the legacy that he's after, the legacy that we're all working for is to revitalize this economy and the country in such a way that the -- there's new vitality that American compact that say s if you work hard you can get ahead.", "docId": "130120pmt", "aSentId": 252, "question": "What would you love to see his legacy end up being after four more years?", "qSentId": 251}, {"answer": "Well, you know, I'm going to point to his own words.", "docId": "130120pmt", "aSentId": 311, "question": "What would you say they would be for him?", "qSentId": 310}, {"answer": "Immigration reform.", "docId": "130120pmt", "aSentId": 358, "question": "What else do you see as priorities?", "qSentId": 357}, {"answer": "Well, I think he's already made that clear.", "docId": "130120pmt", "aSentId": 386, "question": "Do you think the president has the political clout and the personal drive to try and pursue an assault weapons ban if it looks like he can't?", "qSentId": 385}, {"answer": "Well, you know, let's see.", "docId": "130120pmt", "aSentId": 389, "question": "Can he succeed?", "qSentId": 388}, {"answer": "I'm splendid, thank you.", "docId": "130120pmt", "aSentId": 436, "question": "How are you?", "qSentId": 435}, {"answer": "I'm extremely honored to be talking to you, actually.", "docId": "130120pmt", "aSentId": 438, "question": "And you?", "qSentId": 437}, {"answer": "Well, I think he's done the best he could.", "docId": "130120pmt", "aSentId": 458, "question": "And how do you think he's done, President Obama, in his first term and what would you like him to do more of in his second term?", "qSentId": 457}, {"answer": "Thank you.", "docId": "130120pmt", "aSentId": 474, "question": "What advice do you think he would have given the president for his second and final term of office?", "qSentId": 473}, {"answer": "Well, just -- I thought it was very moving and you got a nice call-out there from her.", "docId": "130120pmt", "aSentId": 535, "question": "What did you make of what she said and in particular about what Martin Luther King may have said to Barack Obama?", "qSentId": 534}, {"answer": "I'm great, man.", "docId": "130120pmt", "aSentId": 556, "question": "Nick Cannon, how are you?", "qSentId": 555}, {"answer": "I mean, it's outstanding.", "docId": "130120pmt", "aSentId": 574, "question": "For you as a young black American, what does it mean to you, that day, the significance of both these great men being commemorated on this day?", "qSentId": 573}, {"answer": "I mean, the millennial generation really is a generation of young people who want to do better and all about empowerment.", "docId": "130120pmt", "aSentId": 583, "question": "What should the president be doing, though, to get more people like you to get up there and live the dream again?", "qSentId": 582}, {"answer": "I think it's talent.", "docId": "130120pmt", "aSentId": 592, "question": "ANNON: What does that have to do with talent, Piers?", "qSentId": 591}, {"answer": "She's just as beautiful.", "docId": "130120pmt", "aSentId": 606, "question": "Is she as attractive as last time I saw her?", "qSentId": 605}, {"answer": "Well, I've got to tell you, in 1840, William Henry Harrison got elected and the inaugural in '41 and did not wear a coat.", "docId": "130120pmt", "aSentId": 631, "question": "Tomorrow, talk me through what's actually going to happen?", "qSentId": 630}, {"answer": "Well, remember, like Dr. King, he's won a Nobel Peace Prize, he's an international figure and the world is going to be watching tomorrow.", "docId": "130120pmt", "aSentId": 658, "question": "How can he force through his agenda in a smart way?", "qSentId": 657}, {"answer": "Yet to be seen because of the way the money, I think.", "docId": "130120pmt", "aSentId": 669, "question": "We get the feeling that the Americans perhaps slight realized that continuing to be at war with the president isn't necessarily in the national interest?", "qSentId": 668}]